CAMELLIA ALFINA HANIF

085740543263 | camelliaalfina@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/camellia-alfina/ | https://github.com/camelliaaa03

Depok, Sleman, Daerah Istimewa Yogyakarta

An outstanding fresh graduate student with a track record of academic and extracurricular success. Extensive experience in leadership, particularly in higher education and organizational environments. Working across departments, with faculty, administrators and students is a strength. Communication skills demonstrated by involvement in the organizational world. Have experience with design software but currently focus on software development area.

Work Experiences

Widya Robotics (PT Widya Inovasi Indonesia) - Sleman, Yogyakarta

Feb 2023 - Jun 2023

Software Developer-Internship

• Design DFD and ERD as needed. Implement API design into code. Creating UI and API Integration. Documenting code, updating code using git repository. Learn to create projects by collaborating with other divisions. Deploy or release applications for free. Understand ORM concepts for database implementation.

Evio Multimedia - Sleman, Yogyakarta

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019

Internship

Handling, carrying out daily tasks and field work, ensuring a high level of productivity and progress. Work to maintain an outstanding
attendance record, consistently arrive at work ready to start work immediately. Quickly learn new skills and apply them to everyday tasks,
such as learning to use and maintain multimedia tools and SOPs in working as a documentation service provider. Increase efficiency and
productivity, solve problems, improve operations and maximize in providing outstanding documentation services.

Education Level

Dicoding Academy - Bandung, Indonesia

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Certificate in Studi Independen Bersertifikat, 87.98/100.00

• Develop soft skills related to time scheduling, critical/design thinking, effective communication, and digital branding. Learn the basics of programming to become a software developer, especially an Android developer, through related material. Learn the basics of Android application development from beginner to intermediate. Do the Submission and Capstone project/final project

Universitas Teknologi Digital Indonesia - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Sep 2020 - Oct 2023 (Expected)

Associate Degree in Application Software Engineering, 3.96/4.00

• Building a software application using the Java programming language in the Project 1 course in semester 2. Designing and building a simple mobile application using the Kotlin language and Android Studio as a Final Project assignment in the Native Mobile Programming course, semester 4. Create and design databases, build an information system website in Project 2 course in semester 4

SMK NEGERI 1 KLATEN - Klaten, Jawa Tengah

Jun 2017 - Jun 2020

High School Diploma in Multimedia, 84.14/100.00

- Top 5 in Multimedia major
- Becoming Deputy Chairperson of the Youth Red Cross at SMKN 1 Klaten 2018 □ 2019

Organisational Experience

Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa - Universitas Teknologi Digital Indonesia, Yogyakarta

Aug 2022 - Aug 2023

Kementrian Kominfo

Create, design, and present work programs from concepts to solutions for organizational and campus needs. Designing Instagram posts on
certain big events and holidays, making pamphlets, banners, and posters for organizational and university-level events. Carry out
organizational work programs within the scope of inter-student and university environments

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Soft Skills: Time Scheduling, Critical/Design Thinking, Effective Communication, Digital Branding.
- Hard Skills: Adobe CC, CorelDraw, Canva, Android Studio
- Certificate of Competence BNSP (2022): Programming and Software Development